You know, when Michelle Obama famously said, when they go low, we go high, I never really got down with it because I was just like, yeah, but see, respectability politics means going high means like being like, you know, buttoned up and quiet and prim.
And that that don't win against the people going for your ankles.
So what I say is when they go low, we get loud.
That's what I love about these progressive Democrats.
OK, they're saying we're going to be loud.
Jasmine Crockett, loud.
Cori Bush, loud.
Jamal Bowman, loud.
Ilhan Omar, loud and witty.
Ayanna Pressley, Max Frost, Hakeem Jeffries, loud, loud, loud.
AOC, the loudest.
Right.
Get loud.
And when I say loud, I mean amplifying the freaking facts and doing so with sass.
Because if there's one thing the Republicans got besides caucasity is they got people watching.
Well, you know what?
The people who are doing the right thing, we need to have folks paying attention to when they go low.
We get loud.